Jose Antonio Padron



josepadron.go@gmail.com



3103447203



linkedin.com/in/padronjosef

Summary

React Frontend Developer with experience working on different web programming projects and solid knowledge in interface designing (UI).

Knowledge in JavaScript, React. JS and preprocessors such as SaSS & Stylus.

Design of user interfaces (UI), with programs like ADOBE XD and FIGMA.

- English C1.
- REACT.
- REDUX.
- BOOTSTRAP.
- ADOBE XD, FIGMA.
- COPYWRITING.
- GIT y Git Flow.

Pixel perfect, lifelong learner and tech lover.

- ** Personal Portfolio: https://padronjose.com
- ** GitHub: https://github.com/padronjosef
- ** Behance: https://www.behance.net/josepadron

Experience



Community Relations

Platzi

Jun 2020 - Feb 2021 (9 months)

Leading developer communities, UX Interviewing, UI Designing and creating graphic assets.

Customer Success

Platzi

Sep 2019 - Jun 2020 (10 months)

Student Coaching, Creating learning paths, Customer Experience and Training peers.

Fullstack Web Developer

Sistemas C3

Jan 2019 - Oct 2019 (10 months)

Web application development using JavaScript, CSS and React.js

- SPA development with React Js.
- Implementation of Redux in projects.

- Development of frontend applications for the creation of dynamic and customizable forms to record analyses.
- Deploy of developments in GitHub and GIT Pages.
- Design web interfaces using adobe XD.

Co-founder & CEO

Gden Technology Oct 2018 - Dec 2018 (3 months)

Computer Assistant

SERICINCOL SAS Sep 2017 - Oct 2018 (1 year 2 months)

Education

Santiago Mariño Polytechnic University Institute

Degree in Engineering, Electrical, Electronic and Communications Engineering Technology/Technician 2012 - Present

Licenses & Certifications

Advanced English Level - Centro Venezolano Americano del Zulia. CEVAZ

Git and GitHub Professional - Platzi

4546cf55-a075-4418-94ff-12af94e3a5ac

Frontend Developer - Platzi b826276f-0916-4925-9d17-8c26cf3aca63

Skills

GitHub • React.js • Bootstrap • responsive design • Web Development • Aplicaciones web • UI • User Experience (UX) • HTML5 • Git